I sit from that dog.
This dog is a good river person.
Well, that language I see.
They were all, we just kept going back and forth.
When I was like, those same emails.
They just kept going back and forth.
I've just thought of this as a continuation.
Sorry.
That's me.
It's all together.
All together.
All together today's meeting.
Especially in the mountains.
It's not been recognized now.
You tell me the authority.
I am two as an indication.
My father is a sacred heart, Catholic Church,
Hall, and so being your father.
The name of the father and a person and not the Holy Spirit.
God, we thank you for rebealing yourself to us.
In the incarnation of Jesus the Christ,
who lived in my last suffered, died, rose,
and ascended for the salvation of our souls.
We learned at times of forgiveness and distortions of the truth.
In the midst of the reality of the challenges of our times,
continue to illuminate the world with your good news.
Open our ears, eyes, minds and hearts.
To receive and promote truth, beauty and goodness.
In the unprotected world, we ask your blessing on the city of Miami.
These city leaders, administrators, representatives, and citizens unite
and to start in your holy will for us.
Enjoy the implement yet for your glory and the benefit of our community.
We make this great and Jesus' name.
Thank you.
I pledge allegiance to the pride of the United States.
And to the Republic for which is thanks.
One nation under God, individual, with liberty and justice for all.
Thank you.
I'm full of public and for the unscheduled post of appearances.
And I wanted to ask you to address the capsule on the agenda.
I'm a father's consent.
I'm a member of the office.
I'm recommending item 6 and 7 for the consent agenda, which are claims and minutes.
Questions on any of those?
I'm going to take a motion.
A second.
Second.
Go call please.
Justin.
Aye.
First.
Second.
Aye.
I'm made to amend section 24 to 6 for the billing tables.
And establishing electric grade schedules to allow for the correction of a formatting error.
How much to rent?
Just to be real quick.
What happened with me?
And Jackson did the background band Jackson did the race study as a band that was the
job for the band in the 2016-2017.
Everything was fine, correct, and everything like that.
I copied the table, but he had two of the ordinance, everything was fine except the end of
the end of the race, the kilowatt hours and the end of the race were around the two places
just in a pool.
And it's necessary that we do this, and back to what makes it the next, the rate increase
is made low enough, but it's a skimmerer, and we prepare the ordinance, and that's
not it.
Okay, so do we have a motion to amend?
Let's go make motion.
And a second.
Second.
Low call.
Forster.
Western.
Lewis.
Hi.
Johnson.
Shots.
Thanks, David.
The courts are in your packet, they're in the questions, and I'm ten is trusty community
announcements in the announcements, roadway, sweetheart, dinners tonight, item 11 is a German.
We have most children.
Make motion.
And second.
Low call.
Please.
Forster.